A tall, bald figure in a sweeping green cape stands with his back turned, looking out a large window at a mountainous landscape. The opulent room is lined with tall mirrors and potted plants.
A ghostly face appears in the glass.
His own smooth, elongated face returns.
He stands in a mirrored hallway. A screaming face appears in the glass.
The reflection shifts to a floating brain.
He strides past the mirrors. His long green cape flows behind him, trailing over the dark floor.
He stares at his own reflection.
Bathed in brilliant white light, Horatio stands at the top of a grand staircase.
Below him, two rows of identical clones line the base of the stairs.
The clones stand at attention, looking up at their leader. They are gathered in a massive hall with towering pillars. Huge windows reveal a dark planet in the starry void of space.
Everything fades to black.